Jane.
Jane? Care to join us?
The Moon's at perigee
closest to the Earth.
- It's beautiful, isn't it?
- Yes, it is.
- But the victim is over here.
- I know.
Work.
Victim's name's Eleanor Artega,
shot in the chest.
There were reports
of gunshots around 11:00.
- Is she from the neighborhood?
- ID gives an address across town
but one of the Sac PD officers
said she grew up in the neighborhood.
Her mother runs a grocery
a few blocks away.
Pretty dress. Maybe she was coming
from some kind of event, wedding?
Performance, more like it.
She's a musician.
- Some kind of stringed instrument.
- Because?
Because of the calluses
on her fingertips
and the faint piney scent
of rosin on her dress.
Been a couple of gang
initiation killings in the area.
Could be another one.
I'll talk to the Sac PD Gang Unit
- see who's active.
- We'll canvass the looky-loos.
Hydrangea petal.
Interesting decoration
for a gang slaying
unless the crips have
taken up flower arranging
which I can definitely see
the therapeutic benefits of.
- Thank you.
- Evidence, I believe.
Come on.
And I'm looking for current information
on Norteño gangs in the northeast.
Call me back as soon as possible.
Thanks.
- Hey.
- Damn, man.
You see I'm walking here, right?
- You walked into me.
- Hell I did.
You need to get behind the line.
Police only here.
- Trying to find out who killed that lady?
- You know somethin' about it?
Do I look like a snitch to you?
Keep walkin'.
Go on.
Anything would be useful,
so if you wouldn't mind, just...
Just give us a call and, uh,
thank you very much for your time.
I know it's slow,
but it's how the work is done.
Yeah, I could point out someone
that knows something useful
- with 25 words or less.
- Oh, really?
Count 'em.
Evening.
I have $100 for information
about the victim.
$100.
It's not $100.
Just $1...
for information.
Any takers?
25.
The point being...
The gentleman in the plaid
shirt with the beanie
didn't even consider raising his hand.
That means he has information
that not even $100 can buy.
Sir? Uh, you in the plaid
we're gonna have to ask you
some questions.
Cho, we got a runner! Get the car!
Head off around the block!
Someone took my keys.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Stop the car!
Thanks for the ride, sucka!
Come on, Starsky,
let's go get him. I'll drive.
Stay over here!
Gonna walk home?
Ms. Artega, we're very sorry
for your loss
but we need to ask you some
questions about your daughter.
I have work to do.
Ma'am, what did Eleanor do
for a living?
She was a concert violinist
with the orchestra.
Dawn, I said the first shelf for these.
Sorry, Ms. Artega.
First chair violin
the concertmaster
second to the conductor himself.
Youngest in symphony history.
- You must have been very proud.
- Proud, yes.
I was her manager.
We were a team.
Do you know why Eleanor was
in the neighborhood last night?
She came here.
She had given a solo performance
a special event. She wanted
to tell me about it.
Can you think of anyone
who may have wanted to harm her?
A boyfriend maybe?
She wasn't seeing anyone.
No time.
She used to have a boyfriend.
Orlando Yglesias.
Gangbanger.
They dated about a year or so.
Why would he wanna hurt her?
Eleanor broke it off six months ago.
He wouldn't leave her alone.
He called, came to the apartment.
We had to get a restraining order!
Dawn!
Mop!
How am I gonna clean this up?
How am I gonna...
Oh, my Ellie!
Oh, my baby.
Why did they do this to you?
Why?
"Hey, boss."
So I confirmed that Eleanor Artega
played a private event the night
that she was murdered.
Apparently celebrating
the, uh, recent purchase
by a collector of a, uh...
Wait for it...
"A Brescian Stradivarius violin."
I'm assuming that's a good one.
What about the boyfriend?
Orlando Yglesias, he's got a sheet,
some low-level stuff.
He runs with a Norteño gang
the, uh...
Lincoln Avenue Hermanos.
Eleanor did have
a restraining order on him.
This is the guy that fled
the scene last night
the one that Jane picked out
from the crowd.
Call Sac PD Gang Unit.
Tell them we need any help
- they can give finding this guy.
- Okay, you got it.
Jane?
Jane.
We've got a little homicide
investigation going on here.
You care to join us?
Yeah, I'm, I'm a little
busy right now.
Brahms' Concerto in D Major.
Eleanor's the soloist.
She's very good,
very elegant, uh, rubato.
Music later.
We have a viable suspect...
The victim's ex-boyfriend.
Meh. Wild goose chase, I hope.
You hope? Why?
Well, because if it is the boyfriend
then it's is boring
tragic, but dull
which is to be avoided at all costs.
Where you going?
Jane?
You Cho?
- That's right.
- Beller, Sac PD.
Anthony Rome. I picked him up
on Bellwood in the northwest.
- Got your car, too. It's on its way.
- Thanks.
Juvenile Services is sending
someone to take him in?
They're backed up.
They can't process him
for 48 hours at the least.
Social worker says
his mother passed away.
His father's in jail.
She thinks we should release him
back to his foster family.
What gang put you up to this?
I don't belong to a gang.
Stealing a cop car,
that's an initiation.
You're jumping in with somebody.
Who?
Beasty Mob? True Heights Villains?
Sir, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Hang on to him. Juvenile Services'll get
to him eventually.
Yeah. No, I have a court
appearance today.
I gotta unload him.
He's all yours.
- I okayed it with your boss already.
- You're joking.
No joke.
Thanks for your help, Officer Beller.
- We appreciate the assist.
- No problem.
- Boss...
- Sac PD are not babysitters.
He stole your keys.
He's your problem.
Make sure he doesn't take
anything else.
Sir, you gotta believe me
when I say how sorry I am.
Don't talk.
- No, really, I'm sorry.
- Not buying it.
Come on.
- Whatever, punk.
- That's more like it.
Mr. Jane?
Hi. I'm Kieran Carruthers
the company's outreach assistant.
Front office said I might find you here.
You're no bureaucrat.
You're a musician.
Yes, I'm the principal oboist.
Definitely oboesque.
Concertmaster sits, uh, here, yes?
Yes.
Interesting bookmark.
- Yeah, looks like an expensive one.
- Really?
Yeah.
You know, if you tell me what you're
looking for, I might be able to help.
I'm looking for a killer.
I'm sorry.
Eleanor's killer? Here?
You're musicians,
professional obsessives.
Most kids spend
their teen years having fun.
You spent them practicing scales.
It's a noble pursuit but as a result,
you're all a little nutty.
Well, uh, okay,
I don't know if I'd say that.
There's a definite air
of unrest in the room.
- What is that about?
- Right.
We're supposed to start our season
a day after tomorrow.
Opening night, big fund-raising
meet and greet with our donors.
Some of us thought we should
postpone because of Eleanor
but the, uh, maestro didn't agree.
Your conductor...
A tyrant?
Vincent Manheiser.
I wouldn't say he's a tyrant. He's just...
not nice.
All right, let's get to work.
See for yourself.
Come on, people. Let's go.
Haven't got all day.
Up, up, up. Come on.
All right.
- Constance.
- Yes, maestro?
You will take Eleanor's seat
as concertmaster.
You've not shown any of her
natural gifts of leadership
but under the circumstances,
we shall have to make do, yes?
- I'll do my best.
- Ariel.
Your keen lust for advancement
will be gratified.
- Second seat for you.
- Yes, maestro.
All right, everyone.
Ready?
From the top.
And...
And tension.
Forte.
Yep. Orlando Yglesias.
Okay. Thanks.
Gang Unit's gonna ask around
check out where the victim's
ex-boyfriend hangs.
Good.
There you go.
I can't eat this.
- Why not?
- I'm a vegetarian.
Now it's vegetarian.
Hey. Pick that up.
You better not mess with Cho, man.
He used to be an Avon Park Playboy.
- You were a playboy?
- Oh, yeah. That's right.
Then you should know my dad...
Lawrence Rome.
Runs with the South Side Mafia.
- Never heard of him. I'll be right back.
- All right.
Wayne, I'm getting coffee.
Want some?
Uh, no, thanks.
Hey.
- What is this?
- What?
"I want you, baby. Come to me"?
- Is this some kind of a joke?
- I didn't send that.
- Well, it's on your phone.
- Well, my phone is on my desk.
Hey.
Who's watching the kid?
Hey!
Nice try.
Let's go.
- I had him.
- Yeah.
- You can't do this. I'm a minor.
- Too bad.
I know I shouldn't have messed
with you.
I can't be here.
I gotta go, for real.
Gang Unit just called back.
They say Orlando's crew hangs
at 8th and Market.
We should go sit on it.
You're looking
for Orlando Yglesias, right?
I know him.
He's from the neighborhood.
You ain't gonna find him
at 8th and Market.
Why not?
'Cause that's where
the Hermanos hang.
Orlando's not with them no more.
- Gang Unit says different.
- They don't know.
Jumped into a new gang
a couple months ago.
Yeah? Which one?
Cut me loose, and I'll tell you.
The Loco Pimps.
House on Lex and Tremont,
that's their spot.
Gang Unit says the information's
six months old.
Kid could be right.
Wouldn't hurt to check it out.
Lex and Tremont's close.
If Orlando doesn't show up
we'll swing by the other location.
If you get him, you'll let
me out, right?
Let's go.
You're dragging, people!
Stay in tempo!
Off the string.
Stop!
Stop. Stop.
Ariel.
B-flat? It's ridiculous, even for you.
While we're on the subject,
Ann, Carol, you're dragging.
Trumpets, measure 37...
Soggy.
I thought it sounded
perfectly lovely. Bravo.
- You're awfully picky, aren't you?
- Who are you?
Never mind. Go. Leave. Now.
I'm with the CBI.
I'm here about the murder.
Uh, if you'll please wait outside...
- You hate being interrupted, don't you?
- As a matter of fact, I do.
Interesting. I have one question,
then I'll leave.
I know it was you that murdered
Eleanor Artega.
I just need to know why, Vincent.
Why did you kill her?
You are crazy.
That is exactly, exactly what
I thought you would say
now I know for sure.
Yes.
You, sir
are a cold-blooded murderer...
And you will get what you deserve.
I did not kill Eleanor Artega.
- Are you sure of that?
- Very sure.
- Meh. Well, it's worth a try.
- Worth a try?
Yeah, the old "It was you" gambit.
Guilty people often fold up
at that point...
Guilty people with
a conscience, that is
which means you're either innocent
or you're a cold, heartless monster.
Or both.
This is an outrageous
abuse of authority.
Yes, yes, I know. Don't go getting
on your high horse.
It still might be you, and if it is...
justice will find you.
What?
We're wasting our time.
Orlando's not gonna show up.
The kid played us.
Sounded like he knew
what he was talking about.
He knows how to sell it.
Ah, he doesn't seem that bad to me.
I used to be that kid.
Any chance to mess
with a cop, I'd do it.
Hey, check it out.
- That's Orlando, isn't it?
- Yeah. Go. Go.
CBI.
Let me see your hands. Do it.
Tell me about Eleanor.
Orlando, you wanna talk
after spending the night
in a holding cell, that's your right
but tomorrow morning
I am still gonna be asking you
the same questions.
What you wanna know?
You were an unlikely couple.
Eleanor was in the orchestra.
She was moving her way up.
You weren't.
Then she dumps you.
Must have been stressful.
- Did it make you angry?
- Yeah, here we go.
- Jamming me up for this.
- I'm just askin'.
I wasn't angry.
Eleanor was all about music, always.
Wasn't gonna let me or anyone else
get in the way of that.
- I respected that.
- Then why'd you keep calling?
Going over to her apartment?
We were cool.
There was no reason not to hang.
Except a restraining order.
Her mother made her do that.
She told me.
Her mom thought I was moving in again
'cause I came by a couple times.
If you're such a stand-up guy
why did you run from the crime scene?
A cop calls me out, what I'm gonna do?
I wouldn't hurt El.
Didn't want nothin' but good for her.
Believe it, don't...
I don't control you.
I talked to the clerk of the judge
who issued the restraining order.
Orlando's right.
Eleanor did ask for it
but her mother was the driving force.
That's not what Isabella said.
Also, I checked Eleanor's e-mails.
Eleanor fired Isabella as her manager
and hired a new one
just a couple weeks ago.
I bet that didn't go over well
with the mom.
New manager says Eleanor
and her mother weren't speaking.
They spoke before she died.
Go talk to Isabella again.
- Find out what they really said.
- Okay, I'm on it.
You'll sleep here.
The door will be locked
but there's someone down the hall.
You need anything,
just bang on the door, okay?
But I'm leaving tomorrow, right?
Depends on when Juvenile Services
gets here.
Juvenile Services?
You said you'd let me go
if I gave you Orlando.
- We had a deal.
- There was no deal.
Come on, man.
Don't punk out on me.
I'm not kidding.
I need to get out of here.
Well, you should've thought of that
before you stole a car.
- No, I've got business.
- It'll have to wait.
- Hey.
- Let me go!
Get off me!
Get off of me, man!
Let me go!
- Hey. Stop. Stop.
- Get off of me, man!
- Easy.
- Get off of me!
Look at me. Look at me.
What's this really about?
I'm not leaving until you tell me.
My dad got arrested.
They say he robbed a liquor store
but he didn't.
All right.
He didn't.
He's got an alibi.
Dude named Jayden Stephens.
But Jayden won't come forward.
He's got warrants
out on him, so he's hiding.
But my dad's going on trial next week.
I can't find Jayden.
My dad's going to prison.
That's why I stole your car.
Jayden's running
with the True Heights Villains.
I was thinking
if I can jump in with them
they'd tell me where he's hiding.
Figured they'd know.
You were joining a gang
to get your father outta prison.
Yeah.
Try to get some sleep.
We know Eleanor fired you
as her manager.
- Why didn't you tell us that?
- I didn't think it was important.
Well, you must've talked about it
the night Eleanor came here
and she was killed.
We did.
She wanted to make up. I didn't.
I should've, but I didn't.
So the last time you spoke, you fought?
Are you asking if I killed
my daughter?
No, ma'am, I'm just trying
to get the facts straight.
Yes, she is.
I mean, come on, you are.
Most kids never make it out
of this neighborhood.
Eleanor did
because I gave her everything
so she could have a better life.
- Why would I hurt her?
- Grace, it's clear as day.
Isabella had nothing to do
with her daughter's death.
More importantly,
was Eleanor into cats?
Cats? No.
What about ancient Egypt, pyramids?
Mummies?
No. She never talked to me
about Egypt.
Okay.
Thanks. Let's roll.
"And I look forward to seeing all of you
tomorrow night"
"as our 73rd season begins."
So to all our donors, our board members
our most loyal supporters
I say thank you.
Is that for Ariel?
More of a red wine girl, I would think.
How'd you know this was for her?
Well, clearly,
you've got a thing for her.
Word to the wise,
she likes the bad boys.
- Oh, you're back.
- Mm.
- Don't let Vincent see you.
- I think I can take him.
Oh, can I watch?
That was fun last time.
This is not a joke, Ariel.
I'm following up on an important clue.
It could very well break the case.
Well, come on.
You're gonna tell us, right?
- He can't, Ariel.
- Oh, we won't say anything.
- Promise.
- I'd like to know.
Well, I suppose
you're gonna hear soon enough.
Eleanor was in a relationship
with someone from the orchestra.
I suspected as much.
Who was it?
- Uh, I can't...
- It couldn't be Douglas, could it?
Or Howard?
Think bigger. That's all I'm saying.
It wasn't...
- No.
- Are you serious?
Deadly.
And he was abusing her...
sexually.
- That's awful.
- Yes.
- Oh, my...
- I don't see it.
ID please.
"Mr. Rome, I'm Kimball Cho
with the CBI."
Your son Anthony tells me
you're innocent
of the charge you're facing.
Is that true?
- Anthony told you that?
- Yeah.
How you know my son?
That's not important right now.
Why the hell do you care
about any of this?
I'm giving you a chance to say
you didn't do the crime.
- You're not gonna take it?
- No. No, I didn't do it.
DA says you did.
Yeah, a store owner
picked me out of a lineup.
Bad witness ID that's all.
But you know how hard
that is to beat, right?
And you've robbed
a lotta stores, haven't you?
- Not anymore. That is all behind me.
- Since when?
Since Anthony's mother
passed about a year ago.
I've been trying to step up, do better.
Look, I even got a new construction job.
And you run with the South Side Mafia.
How do they feel about you
steppin' up?
I'm jumping out as soon as
I put all this behind me.
You've had a year to jump out.
What are you waiting for?
Man, the hell with you!
You don't know me!
DA offered you two years.
You could do that much time easily.
Why'd you turn it down?
Two years of my boy in foster care
out there on the streets?
He would be dead or in a cell
with me.
No. I been gone too long.
I have got to get outta here.
Tell me about Jayden Stephens.
I got your message.
- Just in time. The fun will soon begin.
- What's going on?
It's just horrible, isn't it?
- What is, ma'am?
- Our conductor...
has been having an illicit relationship
with our poor, dear Eleanor.
No.
Yes.
And he hit her.
- Allison! Excuse me.
- You're excused.
You. Why?
Lure out the real lover.
Oops. Gotta go.
Someone in the orchestra had
a passionate
and unrequited crush on Eleanor.
And you know this because?
Cats and Egypt...
Eleanor wasn't into them.
The bookmark, she didn't buy it
for herself
and it's too expensive
for a casual gift.
Someone was trying very hard
to impress her.
Now thanks to the rumor mill
that person thinks that Vincent
was sleeping with Eleanor.
Add in a couple of glasses
of champagne
- and if I haven't missed the mark...
- "You son of a bitch!"
How could you do that to Eleanor?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- Don't lie to me.
- Here we go.
Go home and sober up.
That's enough!
Get off of him! Come on!
Now. Break it up!
Break it up now!
Break it up.
Break it up!
Enough! Enough!
Let me know if you need me
to call for backup.
Oh! Hey!
I said, get your hands off!
Constance, we know you bought
Eleanor that bookmark.
We found the charge
on your credit card records.
You were in love with her, weren't you?
Yes, I was.
When did you tell her?
A few weeks ago.
She was really, really nice, but...
she wasn't interested.
Did that upset you?
I suppose a little.
You have a temper, don't you?
No. Hardly at all.
Oh, you got pretty angry at Vincent.
That was different.
I, I thought...
I heard Vincent hurt Eleanor.
I...
I didn't think that was right.
And what about the night
Eleanor died?
Did you have a temper then?
You knew she was playing that night.
It wouldn't have been
that hard to follow her.
You can't be serious.
I don't think the fact that Vincent
had abused Eleanor
is what upset you.
I think you couldn't stand her
being with somebody else.
No.
All right, then explain this
for me then.
Why was the gun that killed
Eleanor in your car?
What?
A few hours ago,
we found it in your trunk.
That isn't mine.
It's...
Th, that's not mine. It isn't.
That's not really an explanation
of how it got there.
I...
I,I want a lawyer.
Please.
So, Constance.
We're charging her.
Then we can all rest easy.
Say it.
She didn't do it.
We found the weapon in her car.
Didn't do it.
Unless you have actual evidence
that exonerates her
- we have to charge her.
- If she were the killer
she would have exhibited
some measure of guilt.
All I observed was sincere grief.
Actual evidence.
Okay. The gauntlet's
been thrown down.
When you searched Constance's car,
did you notice any flowers?
No. Why?
She's all yours.
Hey, Osvaldo.
How's it going in the DA's office?
Not so good.
We need to talk about Agent Cho.
Ardiles is prosecuting Rome.
I'm told you visited Rome in jail.
Is that true?
- Why do you wanna know?
- Why...
Uh, because Mr. Rome's lawyer
has sent me an updated witness list
with the name Jayden Stephens on
which is interesting
because as far as I can tell
Jayden Stephens is a convenient figment
of Mr. Rome's imagination.
But now according to Mr. Rome's lawyer
even though you have nothing
to do with this
you said you'd track down
this Mr. Stephens
thereby providing
Mr. Rome with an alibi
potentially screwing my case.
That's why I need to know, Agent Cho.
Answer him.
Yes, I did that.
Agent, do you know who, uh, Asante James
and Rodrick Pierce are?
No.
Well, they're only the, uh, top two
lieutenants in the South Side Mafia.
Probably a dozen bodies on each.
Lawrence Rome worked with them.
You want Lawrence to flip?
- Well, that's the idea.
- Lawrence won't flip.
- Really? Why not?
- He knows they'd kill him.
Right. And you know so much
about that?
More than you, I guess.
Agent, do I have to take this upstairs?
- Because I'm ready.
- No, you don't.
Hey, this is not our case.
Rome's attorney or the DA's office
can look for Jayden Stephens.
We should not get involved.
Good.
Then we're in agreement.
We shouldn't get involved.
Got it.
- Where's the kid?
- Juvenile Services just took him.
- "Let go of me, man. Man, let go of me!"
- "Listen, zip your mouth."
- "Let go of me!"
- Hey! Hold on.
Easy, son, easy.
- What's up?
- I'm Agent Cho.
- I'll take the kid off your hands.
- What?
I made a mistake. Let's just forget
I filed a report, okay?
Too late. Paperwork's been filed.
It's my case now.
Besides, it took me an hour to get here.
I'm not going back empty-handed.
Now do you mind?
Hey, hey.
- Give him to me.
- Sorry. Can't do that.
- He hit you. That's battery.
- Are you kidding me?
- I have to process him now. Paperwork.
- Hold on.
- Bye.
- Hey.
- This is bull!
- What are you doing, man?
Be quiet or I'll give you back.
I thought the police work was over.
Oh, I just stopped by
to congratulate you.
I'm sorry. Me?
You are the new concertmaster,
aren't you?
Now that Constance is in the pokey.
Thanks.
It's not exactly something
that deserves congratulations.
When you heard about the promotion
what was the first thought
that popped into your head?
Sadness... relief.
You know, just last week
I was thinking of leaving here
and trying my luck elsewhere.
Now...
Well, you got what you wanted.
You're pleased and...
yet you feel guilty.
It's perfectly understandable.
I need to get back to rehearsing.
Don't mind me.
Excuse me.
Do you know
if there's a good florist nearby?
What up, Jay?
Jayden Stephens?
Who wants to know?
Hey, CBI. Let me see your hands.
All right.
We're gonna talk
about Lawrence Rome.
We can talk. Let's talk.
Give me your arms!
What'd I do?
Get up.
What the hell's going on here?
- Get outta the way.
- Or what?
Keep breathing. You'll be fine.
For you.
- Does it squirt water?
- No. No trick.
Maybe just a little trick.
Catch the killer.
- With a hydrangea?
- Yeah.
How?
Well, wouldn't that be spoiling
the fun?
For you.
Spoiling the fun for you.
That's the fun that matters.
We're dropping charges
against Lawrence Rome.
I see.
Personally, I think the alibi is bogus
but we had to interview
the store owner again.
Now he says, uh,
maybe his ID was wrong.
Maybe it wasn't Lawrence Rome.
Whole thing's gone down the toilet.
We had an agreement.
I agreed I shouldn't help.
Didn't say I wouldn't.
From now on, you get nothing
from the DA's office.
No favors, no help...
and not just you, but every
agent in this unit.
You have screwed things
for your people, my friend.
Six months from now, Lawrence Rome
will be back inside
for ripping off another liquor store
his kid'll be back in foster care
and the South Side Mafia
will be stronger than ever.
You're wrong.
You wanna bet on that?
On the stage
either side of the stairs.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Kieran!
You're my rock! Never a wrong note.
What is going on?
I'm sorry, maestro, I just...
I'm not feeling very well.
What is the matter?
I can answer that.
What's he doing here?
Fabulous suit, by the way.
Kieran's not so much feeling sick
as he is feeling guilty...
Sick with guilt because
it was him that killed Eleanor.
Come on.
Hydrangeas don't lie.
Well, if they could speak,
they wouldn't lie.
What are you talking about?
Somebody gave Eleanor
a bouquet of hydrangeas
the night of the murder.
"After you shot Eleanor, you swiped them"
"leaving behind a single petal."
And when you saw them, you couldn't
help remembering that night.
You felt guilty.
It killed your concentration.
Come on. Constance killed her.
You found the gun in her car.
Because you framed her.
Precisely.
The question remains...
Why would a man kill
the first chair violinist
and then frame the second chair?
Because with the first and second chair
out of the picture
the third takes first.
Ariel.
Kieran here has a little crush on you.
Well, let's not beat around
the bush here, Kieran.
It's more of an obsession.
He'd heard that you'd been thinking
about leaving the orchestra.
Then he would lose you.
So he had to shake things up.
- Kieran?
- It's not true.
Okay, this is because I played
a few wrong notes? This is crazy!
He told you that you'd eventually
become first chair, didn't he?
It was just a feeling
that he had, a little hunch.
He always had faith in you.
- Ariel. No, Ariel.
- You stay away from me.
Wait, Ariel, wait.
No, no. Wait. Wait.
- Ariel, listen. No, Ariel. Ariel, wait!
- No! Calm down.
- I just wanna make you happy!
- That's enough.
- Maestro, take five.
- Okay.
Break, everyone.
Eleanor was nothing compared
to Ariel.
She didn't have the technique.
So after rehearsal that night, I followed
Eleanor to her performance.
Why'd you take the flowers?
He didn't think Eleanor deserved them.
Isn't that right?
Ariel is ten times the player.
She deserved the recognition.
If I had to give it to her
so be it.
Very gallant.
Still, I wouldn't expect a conjugal.
Dad!
Oh, what's up, man?
- I missed you so much.
- Oh!
Look at you.
God, look at you.
Come on.
I missed you.
Lawrence.
All right. Give me a minute.
Okay.
I talked to the Gang Unit.
If you haven't jumped out in a month
they'll let me know.
I said I would.
You have a chance, don't mess it up.
What's this punk saying to you, Dad?
Easy. Easy, little man.
We just, we just talking.
Hey, Cho. We got a new one.
Heading out in a minute.
Thanks, Mr. Rigsby.
- I really appreciate everything.
- Uh, yeah. Um, no problem.
That was weird.
I barely talked to the kid.
Check your pockets.
My wallet. Damn it!
Hold the elevator!
Mind if I...